http://www.saad.org.uk/index.php/privacy-policy-statements

SAAD, 21 Portland Place, London, W1B 1PY
AboutTrusteesHistoryContact UsLinks
Login
Register
CoursesMeet the Faculty (Lecturers)DentistsNursesDental therapists/ hygienistsView all CoursesSAAD Alumni Practice EvaluationsFAQsElectronic RecordsPrivacy Policy StatementsShopContact Details EventsDigest & NewslettersDocumentsCPDNewPrizes & GrantsEquipment LoanSAAD Assessed Sedation Nurse (SASN) schemeSAAD Assessed Sedationist (SAS) scheme
You are here: Home » Privacy Policy Statements
Login
Normally, you will use your eMail address as your Username to login. If you have forgotten your password, please click on the down arrow below followed by Forgot your password.
Username
Password
Log in
Forgot your password?
Tip: Your username is normally your eMail address
Find out about membership
Remember Me
Close
SAAD Membership
Membership of SAAD is open to any registered medical or dental practitioner or dental nurse whether based in the UK or abroad.
Student membership of SAAD is free for dental and medical undergraduates registered at a university in the UK or Ireland.
Click here to find out more
SAAD Editorial Board
Call for papers!
The Editorial Board welcomes case reports and original papers
Submit by 30th June 2021 for the 2022 Digest
Please refer to the guidelines for authors and the case report template
Privacy Policy Statements
In compliance with the 2018 General Data Protection Regulations, Privacy Policy Statements are provided below for all areas of SAAD activity where we hold data.
SAAD Membership Subscriptions Privacy Policy Statement
SAAD Courses Privacy Policy Statement
SAAD Training Schemes Privacy Policy Statement
SAAD Events Privacy Policy Statement
SAAD 'Register of Interest' Emailing Lists Privacy Policy Statement
SAAD Alumni Privacy Policy Statement
-
If you have any questions about how SAAD is complying with the 2018 General Data Protection Regulations please contact SAAD's Executive Secretary,
Fiona Trimingham, at
fiona@saad.org.uk, or on 01302 846149.
ABOUT SAAD
SAAD is at the forefront of postgraduate teaching of sedation techniques in dentistry.
The Society runs courses for the whole dental team encouraging the safe provision of conscious sedation. Other activities include providing scientific seminars, giving expert advice to other bodies including the Department of Health and the General Dental Council; providing experts for guidelines and standards documents; giving expert evidence to the courts; promoting research in the field of pain and anxiety control and providing individual support and advice to members.
Membership of the society is open to any registered dental or medical practitioner, dental nurse or dental therapist/hygienist.
CLICK HERE TO FIND OUT MORE
